// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "1+1 é?",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "1",
      "4",
      "5",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {answer: "16"
    numb: 2,
    question: "2x2 é?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "22",
      "8",
      "3",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "4x9 é?",
    answer: "36",
    options: [
      "2",
      "13",
      "33",
      "42"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "8+8 É?",
    answer: "16",answer: "16"
    options: [
      "12",
      "11",
      "14",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "2+9 é?",
    answer: "11"
    options: [
      "12",
      "10",
      "18",
      "20"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 6,
    question: "1+4 é?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "1",
      "4",
      "5",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {answer: "16"
    numb: 7,
    question: "2x9 é?",
    answer: "18",
    options: [
      "22",
      "8",
      "3",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "4x4 é?",
    answer: "16",
    options: [
      "2",
      "13",
      "33",
      "42"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "8+1 É?",
    answer: "9"
    options: [
      "12",
      "11",
      "14",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "2+10 é?",
    answer: "12"
    options: [
      "11",
      "10",
      "18",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
